Contact

+917259146846 (Mobile) shashankramaprasad951@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shashank-k-r-82212912b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

Data Structures

Algorithms

Languages

Hindi (Full Professional)

English (Full Professional)

Tamil (Native or Bilingual)

Shashank K R

Software Development Engineer at Handzap | Java | Data Structures | Algorithms | Spring Boot | Microservices

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the Information Technology & Services industry. Skilled in Core Java, C++, JavaScript and Spring Framework. Strong engineering professional with a B.E focused in Information Science from S J B Institute of Technology, BANGALORE.

Experience

Handzap Inc.
Software Development Engineer
March 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)
Bengaluru, India

Infoview Technologies Pvt Limited Software Engineer September 2017 - March 2019 (1 year 7 months) Chennai, India

Education

S J B Institute of Technology, BANGALORE B.E, Information Science/Studies · (2013 - 2017)

Deeksha Centre for Learning PU College Pre University, PCMC · (2011 - 2013)

BET Convent High School · (1999 - 2011)

Activity

07/07/2020, Shashank K R added candidate to Senior Software Engineer